The title of the project, the funniest of everything wins!
Yay!
It's so funny!
What is this!
Boring!
Well, well, well, we're trying to have a planning meeting at least once a week.
That's what we're doing.
But we get a lot of rejections.
No, you're full of rejects.
A lot of rejections.
Of course.
They don't pick up all the rejects.
It's so boring.
I don't know, maybe some slime.
You know, I was just about to say that five years ago.
That's funny.
And it says "Tambalasi".
That's right!
What's with the location?
Sometimes, you know...
It's just an occasional project.
This is really interesting, but isn't it a little too sharp? Or...
or "This is kind of fun, but it's not feasible, is it?
I think there are a lot of projects like that.
And if it's not too bad...
I thought, "Let's have a championship of the same thing.
So, this time
It's okay if it's not feasible.
What?
That's about right.
We'll decide on the most interesting title draw.
I see.
Well...
I'll let you use your head.
I'm going to ask you to use your mind.
Think of a title that you find most interesting.
Think of a title that you think is the most interesting and compelling.
First of all, it's like a YouTube title comedy.
That's right.
But, well, I'm not sure if it's a good idea for me this time.
I've got a good plan for this.
I see.
I see. Why?
What's that? If you have a plan that you think is surprisingly good...
I'll pick it up.
Yes, yes, yes.
Why?
Let's start right away.
The one with the funniest title wins!
I'd like to do it.
All right.
So...
Shall we start?
Let's take it from the person who thought too much.
Maybe Shunichi is strong.
I am.
No, Shunta has a strong title pull.
He's strong, but he's useless.
You know the one I showed you before?
What was it? Shunta's train?
What? The train?
Which line has the best chance of getting out of this championship.
How are we going to test that?
The Yamanote championship is decided.
All right.
Wait a minute.
Here we go!
The first YouTube project.
Yes, sir.
Playing in the water with Paon, the elephant
You're a genius!
You saved the day, didn't you?
Thank you, Jun-chan!
You're talking about yourself!
Yes, sir.
Mr. Owasaru!
I really want to do this.
I've been trying to do Tsumuzi until I get hungry.
I want to do this.
I'd like to do this, too.You mean a project to verify the passage?
Yes, that's right.
You're early.
I've got a lot of projects I want to do.
I drank this one with a senji claw.
Not senji?
I drank the claws from a person's claws like this.
You know, there is such a thing as a claw like a tawase, and you drink it with a senji.
Oh, yes, there is.
I don't know it.
That's the end of the story.
It's a claw!
Sorry.
It was my claw.
Here you go.
Here we go.
Verification.
The championship!
Longest silence after the toast wins.
Tire
Tires.
What do you mean?
Cheers.
You know, this is the part where you say...
You're the kind of guy who says, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't say that.
I'll just say it and lose it.
That's true.
Don't just say it.
I love it. I love it so much.
I'm bit.
Yes, sir.
It's you, Aichi.
Speaking of YouTube...
Slime and Mentos cola.
Looks like it won't happen again.
When you mix all the projects that people who like YouTube like...
Surprise!
Surprise?
What's a surprise?
It's just a word, usually.
You guys have fun today.
Hey!
They're not here.
It's been less than 10 minutes.
A collection of plays
I've had my left leg for a month, and the bad guy wins.
ahaha
Got a place to live
insulation is inevitable
appliances in someone's house who has a reputation for being nice
he gets angry when I break everything
Pfft...
How many days have I been wearing this?
ahaha
I became a cat and sang a cat song
I'm scared of school vacations
I'm going to get my hair removed by O-chan
A-ha-ha-ha
I tried to whiten my teeth until I couldn't see them
I tried whitening my teeth
Find God... how much can you buy me?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to ask all the junior high school students in the country...
I'm going to ask for your help.
Sir?
He's good, he's good, he's good.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's not good!
If it's too funny, it's bad.
That's a good candidate.
That's a good one.
Knee hump
When you get to captain's level...
I'm going to guess... just by looking at him.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, sir.
I'll have a scout from Takeshita-dori scout for you
Ha-ha-ha.Ha-ha-ha!
Oh!
That's funny.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I was scouted on Takeshita-dori.
That's right.
I'll try the opposite.
If you say so.
I'm not a scout.
Audition group
I wonder if you're an audition group scout.
Aaaaah!
Audition group
I don't think they're going to scout me when I walk around town.
This is really interesting.
I hope they do it.
I really want to be scouted.
No, no, no, no, no.
Put on your best clothes. - No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's the hard part, isn't it?
It's not that eggy is better.
Yes, it is.
This is definitely going to be cool.
It's okay.
Okay, I'll go with one here.
I did a fitness workout with a glowing earth mama.
Ha-ha-ha.
Here it is.
I know I'm being a little reckless, but...
But there's a video of me doing fitness with Daichi's mom.
And I was thinking...
This is...
This is my own son's life.
It's really interesting.
As a real son.
I'm gonna get to live it.
This is good, right?
I'm gonna make your dad dance to Milk.
I'm gonna make him dance.
Oh, my God, that's great.
Oh, that's a good one.
It's good for someone's wedding.
Happily Ever After Dance Practice.
Dad's version
Oh, my God.
Dad or some stiff makeup.
Seriously cool stuff.
That's a good one.
I'd love to do a family version.
There's one I can't show my face in, though.
I made my dad sing in one shot.
That's awesome.
I'd love to see that.
Dad's take.
My dad's a great singer.
He's a great singer.
If we were in a band, he'd be the singer.
I'm serious.
Judo and vocals.
He did a little bit after he quit.
I got a tape of the school festival.
On a cassette tape.
I'd record them and send them to him.
Tapes.
I'm not...
I've had a little trouble with it before.
That's the kind of thing I want to do.
I did a milk job.
You know, work experience kind of thing.
And I knew I had to do it.
If I get caught, I'm out immediately.
Okay.
You know that birthday party?
You were a security guard, right?
They didn't know.
That's great.
It's a stand-alone project with Sanohaya.
It's a place name.
Where would they know if I worked with Sanohaya and where?Sanohaya and where and when I work part-time, they'll know.
I'll definitely watch this one.
Best Stage
At a tapioca shop in Harajuku.
They've been doing this for about 3 years.
He's been doing this for about 3 years.
Okay, so...
Actually, I have something to report.
I actually had a part-time job for three years
I've been in the part-time area
Okay.
Too sleepy! How long can I stay awake?
Marginal Nakao Championship
I want to put in a fan wedding.
Great.
If you get caught, you get a sermon right away.
Playing tag with a monk at the temple
Yes, sir.
I want to make my own art.
I'd like to put it on auction with a special order.
I don't know, it's on TV or something.
You know, to decide?
I don't know about art anymore.
It's a good thing if the standard goes up
If I have a chance to snatch it...
You could be an artist.
You know, a certain song version of it.
Make up your own song.
Uh...
But if you put it out there...
Put it out there.
But I don't know... my company...
Stardust or Victor.
Try applying for something.
You know, anonymously.
Anonymous.
Oh, that's nice.
I've also tried submitting a competition for a single.
Wow.
You should write your own song and submit it.
I see.
And it's always a really good single.
It's usually from 100.
Like that ribbon...
How much was it?
200 or so?
That's right.
I was chosen out of about 200 or so.
Oh, really?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I stretched the time to the limit.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Verification.
On the block next to that sidewalk where elementary school kids often walk.
I can cross Japan on foot.
I can't.
I'm just being myself.
It's called YouTube.
Except for you, I watch it.
This is what I want to study.
I want to study.
Not at all.
Well, it's true.
On Japanese TV.
Oh, that's what you mean.
Maybe that's why it's the new TV.
That's for sure, that's for sure.
That's what I want to see.
Yes, yes, yes
You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
It's got to be the first cut.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I mean, we're already...
I thought that's what YouTube was supposed to be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because if it was, you've really been watching it for like 10 years.
That's right.
Dae-chan's
New car
One of yours.
I'm afraid of that too.I'm afraid of that too.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
I'm going.
Oh, no!
Pit in front of the house.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
I'm sorry if I can't use your name, but...
How do you beat Mr. Takei? Do you beat animals?
Oh, my God.
I tried to blow up Daichi's house.
It's definitely a person.
No one's planning this.
If you saw it...
I tried to put Daichi's earphones in like this.
I'm sorry I lied.
You break people's stuff too much!
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God...
I'm going to break it.
Oh, my God.
Earth versus superiors.
I really want to see that.
I can't come back to this job.
Thank you for watching.
Sparkling treasures!
Just one from someone else's house!
How's that?
Awww.
Just one.
Oh my God, it's sour!
I changed the alcohol sanitizer to vinegar.
Awww!
I changed the contents of alcohol disinfectant to vinegar
I'm going to change it to vinegar, aren't I?
Why do you drink vinegar as a sour drink?
Awww!
This vinegar smells good, doesn't it?
Smells good, doesn't it?
It's good for you.
If I put it on my hand...
You're going to get a takazukikon.
Think about it.
Shun-chan was the funniest at first.
You're right.
He's the worst.
That's why you thought about it.
Awww!
Then laugh more, everyone!
Here we go!
This is a little bit...
I'm serious.
This is probably...
Oh, my gosh!
It's going to be a project.
Oh!
It's going!
Too bad
Tic-tac-toe
The championship without looking at the clock!
Awww!
Thank you, Shun-chan!
Here you go.
What are you talking about?
Please hold it.
I'll try.
Tic-tac-toe watch championship.
Which one?
Who's that?
Aww!
I'm pretty sure you're gonna tell me that next time.
Tell me about it.
I don't want to.
That's what you're saying.
It'll be fun.It's definitely interesting.
It's gonna be fun.
You're the one who said that.
You!
Tick-tock.
But it's going to be fun.
Awww!
It was a toy.
Drinking ramen noodles
Accessory making
Awww!
In Sendai
Beef tongue labretan
Quickly Manturn
The World Wide Web
Ita Tata Tata
Chūryoku Championship
At the library
There is a person who is cosplaying as Kang-chan without permission
Awww.
Yes, er.
Like the expensive denim one.
I honestly don't know.
Awww.
But I like it.
I'd like to buy a nice denim like that
I'd like to buy one someday.
It's good stuff.
Oh? You have one of those?
I didn't recognize the expensive ones without the logo.
It's all brand name stuff.
Wow, that's tough.
Yes, Judas.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
eh?
Yes, yes, yes
Awww.
Huh?
Don't tell me what you just said.
Say it.
Uh, I was walking my dog.
What? People who say he's cute... it's really annoying.
Awww!
That's not what you're saying.
Wow, that's...
That's...
Awww!
You're just holding a stray!
I think it's cute
I think it's good if you think it's cute in your mind
Awww...
I think I'm going to say it.
You'll say it?
I usually just say, "That's cute.
Like it's cute.
He says I can squat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll stop time.
They'll think I'm cute.
That's not what I was thinking.
I wouldn't think that if I wasn't thinking it.
It makes me happy.
Yes, I am.
Yes, Mr. Daichi.
I won't write anymore.
It's a pain in the ass.
Huh?
What?
It's pretty lame.
It's okay if it's lame.
What?
Ka-cha! You know what I'm saying?
The key system of the house has changed!
Awww!
How about that?
Let's say, for example, you and Jin are going to do that project...
I have a key to the house with Jin.You have a key to Jin's house, don't you?
I have a key case or something.
I put about 20 keys in the key case or something.
Awww.
I don't know which key it is...
Oh no!
That's what I do.
I don't even put a mark on it, I just ask which one it is every day.
If I let Daichi present a project that would have been rejected if someone else said it, it will be accepted.
Awww!
That's dangerous!
Maybe I'll let Daichi tell you.
Well, I'm off then.
I've got a good subject!
What's this?
What?
Go for it!
I asked the guy from Tarman to do me a favor!
Awww!
Not even me?
Is there anything you can't do?
Is it in order or something?
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
Awww...
I guess it's about time.
I can't think straight anymore.
Then let's end with one last thing.
Let's do one last thing that everyone will find funny.
Let's end with that.
And the winner.
Okay.
We're going to let the earth take us for a ride, and I made a mold.
Awww!
Thank you, Daichi.
I'm sorry, this is really all I could figure out.
The theory that adding people to the zoo has the lowest answer value.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Awww.
That's the worst.
He said it's the worst.
They're probably the least interesting of all the animals.
Life.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Upstairs.
It's normal.
You wear sneakers in the summer.
If you don't wear slips at home, you're not in shape.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about people who wear sneakers at home.
What are you talking about?
I don't get it.
Can I say something cute?
Okay, sure.
Okay.
What?
Grandma's old wisdom.
I'd like to scientifically disprove it.
Awww.
No, you.
Winner
Wait!
Daichi too!
And the earth.
I like this one.
Please.
Ehh...
Warning
Browsing Browsing
Viewing Warning
Hot FoodHot Food
Hot
WOW!
Shun Tan won!
Congratulations!
Awww!
I'll give it a shot.
It'll be fun!
That's so funny!
Grandma's Wisdom.